# Shreeya Zemse Shahasane

9561953443



Wakad, Pune

#### **SUMMARY**

More than 7 years' experience as HR Generalist in the areas of Recruitment, Selection, Pre-employment Joining formalities, Induction, Employee Grievance, Payroll processing, Budgeting, Performance Management, Responsible for various MIS reports like (Payroll MIS, Headcount, attrition, wage cost etc.)

Comprehensive exposure in MS office, Payroll Software (Greythr, People Soft, Keka, & ERP) & other internet application.

Having a flexible and helpful attitude towards work and able to maintain accurate employee record & MIS.

## **Competencies**

- Recruitment & Selection
- Onboarding & Induction
- Payroll Management
- Statutory Compliances

- Performance Management
- Employee Engagement
- Exit Formalities & F&F

#### WORK **EXPERIENCE**

#### **HYT Engineering Pvt. Ltd.**

Senior HR Executive

August 2024 - November 2024

- · Administered monthly payroll for all employees, ensuring accuracy in employee compensation, deductions, and bonus.
- Maintained detailed and accurate records for payroll, attendance, and leave management to facilitate seamless payroll processing.
- Prepared comprehensive monthly MIS reports for management to support data-driven decision-making.
- Addressed and resolved payroll-related queries promptly, enhancing employee satisfaction.
- Drafted critical HR documents, including Appointment Letters, Confirmation Letters, Appraisal Letters, and Experience Letters.
- Managed the full and final settlement process for exiting employees.

#### Wiggles .in (Sixth Sense Retail Pvt. Ltd)

Senior Executive Payroll & Compliance

May 2021 - May 2024

- Took complete ownership of payroll operations for PAN India employees, ensuring timely and compliant processing.
- Managed payroll audits and ensured adherence to statutory compliance requirements, including Tax, PF, ESI, PT, and LWF.
- · Conducted Annual Performance Management System (PMS) exercises, including salary revisions and performance pay calculations.
- · Generated various MIS reports, such as Payroll MIS, Headcount, Attrition, and Wage Cost Analysis.
- · Recommended and implemented system enhancements to optimize payroll and compliance processes.
- Conducted exit interviews to analyze reasons for employee terminations or resignations and implemented corrective measures.

#### Yashada & Vivanta Realty Group

HR Executive

January 2020 - May 2020

- Managed end-to-end recruitment and selection processes, ensuring the acquisition of top talent.
- Designed, developed, and implemented corporate HR policies, including leave policies, HR manuals, and office systems.
- Maintained detailed employee records and important documentation within the MIS database.

#### Cinepolis India Pvt. Ltd.

**HR** Coordinator

June 2016 - August 2019

- Coordinated onboarding processes for new joiners, including drafting Offer Letters, Appointment Letters, Increment Letters, and Experience Letters.
- Conducted full-cycle recruitment, including sourcing candidates from job portals and other channels.
- Maintained daily MIS reports to track recruitment and HR operations effectively.

#### **Empower Recruitments**

HR Executive

October 2015 - April 2016

#### **EDUCATION**

#### A.C.Patil College of Engineering & Management

MMS

2013 - 2015

**Human Resource** 

#### S.N.D.T University, Matunga

Bsc

2010 - 2013

Resource Management

### Personal Details

Date of Birth - 14th August 1992

Marital Status - Married

Languages Know - English, Hindi & Marathi